Muhammad Yousuf

yousufakram5154@gmail.com 03104345154 Lahore, Punjab

Summary

Self-motivated Developer adds high level of experience over more than 2 years collaborating and working on multiple web-based projects. Passionate, hardworking coder with penchant for developing customized interfaces that factor in unique demands for accessibility, reachability and security. Organized approach to meeting multiple, concurrent deadlines. Pulls from active knowledge of current technology landscape to promote best practices in web design.

Experience

Front End Developer

Webbuggs • Lahore, Punjab

09/2022 - Present

- Developed new web and mobile applications that have been deployed across multiple platforms
- Responsible for the design and maintenance of the company's website, including marketing site, promotional site, blog, sales site and customer service site
- · Created new applications from scratch using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

Front End Developer

Qode Matrix • Lahore, Punjab

01/2023 - 04/2024

- Worked closely with clients to gather requirements and translate them into technical specifications for implementation.
- Continuously updated skills through training. courses, workshops, and self-study-staying current on industry trends and emerging technologies.

Associate Software Engineer

UGA1Tech · Lahore, Punjab

04/2023 - 09/2023

- Collaborated with cross-functional learns to develop. test, and deploy high-quality software solutions for clients.
- Participated in sprint planning sessions by estimating task complexity and prioritizing work Items.

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Vue JS, AngularJS, WordPress, JQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Communication Skills, Elementor, Gutenberg, Git, Figma, PHP

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

Virtual University of Pakistan • Lahore, Punjab

06/2023

Bachelor's Degree in Actuarial Science

University of the Punjab • Lahore, Punjab

07/2021